Janice has a question. Who of the six of you has slept with who of the six of you?
賈妮絲有一個問題。你們六個人中誰和你們六個人中誰睡過？
Wow, it's like a dirty math problem.
哇，這就像一道骯髒的數學題。
I'm sorry, the answer there would be none of us.
抱歉，答案是我們沒有人。
Yeah, and you know what? If that doesn't change soon, I'm going to dump you for somebody who puts out.
是的，你知道嗎？如果這種情況不趕快改變，我就會把你甩給一個不喜歡的人。
Come on, over the years, none of you ever got, you know, drunk and stupid?
拜託，這麼多年來，你們沒有人喝醉過、犯過傻嗎？
Well, that's really a different question.
嗯，這確實是一個不同的問題。
I'm sorry, I find it hard to believe that a group of people who spends as much time together as you guys do has never bumped uglies.
抱歉，我很難相信像你們這樣花這麼多時間在一起的一群人從來沒有碰過醜人。
There was that one time that Monica and Rachel got together.
有一次莫妮卡和瑞秋聚在一起。
What? Excuse me, there was no time.
什麼？對不起，沒有時間。
Okay, but let's say there was.
好吧，但我們假設有。
How might that go?
那會怎麼樣呢？
Okay, okay, well then answer me this.
好吧好吧，那就回答我這個吧。
Have any of you ever almost?
你們有人曾經幾乎嗎？
Yeah, I'll take this dog out there.
是的，我會把這隻狗帶出去。
It's like you're always stuck in second gear.
就像你總是被困在二檔一樣。
When it hasn't been your day, week, month, even your year.
當這不是你的一天、一週、一個月、甚至一年的時候。
But I'll be there for you.
但我會在你身邊。
When the rain starts to pour.
當雨開始傾盆而下。
I'll be there for you.
我會在那等你。
Like I've been there before.
就像我以前去過那裡一樣。
I'll be there for you.
我會在那等你。
Oh, that is so unfortunate.
哦，那真是太不幸了。
What?
什麼？
Cute naked guy's really starting to put on weight.
可愛的裸男真的開始變胖了。
Okay, I'll be back in just a minute.
好的，我一會兒就回來。
Oh, Phoebe, I'm sorry that I left lipstick marks on the phone.
哦，菲比，很抱歉我在手機上留下了口紅痕跡。
You didn't leave lipstick marks on the phone.
你沒有在手機上留下口紅痕跡。
Oh, then it must have been you.
哦，那一定是你了。
Bye-bye.
再見。
That's why I moved out.
這就是我搬出去的原因。
Hey, while we're on that, when are you going to tell my sister that you don't live here anymore?
嘿，當我們討論這個問題的時候，你什麼時候要告訴我姐姐你不再住在這裡了？
I think on some level she already knows.
我認為在某種程度上她已經知道了。
Phoebe, she doesn't know that you sneak out every night.
菲比，她不知道你每天晚上都偷偷溜出去。
She doesn't know that you sneak back every morning.
她不知道你每天早上都會偷偷回來。
And she doesn't know that you've been living at your grandmother's for a week now.
她不知道你已經在你祖母家住了一個星期了。
Okay, well, maybe not on those levels.
好吧，也許還沒有達到這些水平。
You have got to tell her, okay?
你必須告訴她，好嗎？
The longer you wait, the harder it's going to be on her.
你等的時間越長，她就越難受。
You're right, you're right.
你是對的，你是對的。
Anyway, listen, tonight's bag is really bulky.
不管怎樣，聽著，今晚的包包真的很大。
So could you sneak some stuff out for me?
那你能幫我偷點東西嗎？
It's just like a clock radio and some cemetery dirt.
它就像一個時鐘收音機和一些墓地的泥土。
Hey.
嘿。
I'm never going to find a roommate, ever.
我永遠不會找到室友。
Well, nobody good?
嗯，沒人好嗎？
Well, let's see.
好吧，讓我們看看。
There was the guy with the ferrets.
那個人帶著雪貂。
That's plural.
那是複數。
Spitter.
隨地吐痰。
Oh, and yes, the guy who enjoyed my name so much
哦，是的，那個非常喜歡我的名字的人
he felt the need to make a little noise every time he said it.
每次他說這句話的時候，他都覺得需要發出一點聲音。
Nice to meet you, Chandler Bing.
很高興認識你，錢德勒賓。
Bing!
賓！
Great apartment, Chandler Bing.
很棒的公寓，錢德勒賓。
Bing!
賓！
So how many more do you have tomorrow?
那麼明天還有多少個呢？
Two.
二。
This photographer who seemed really dull.
這位攝影師看起來真的很遲鈍。
And this actor guy who I'm not sure about
還有這個我不確定的演員
because when he called and I answered the phone, Chandler Bing,
因為當他打電話而我接電話時，錢德勒·賓，
he said, whoa, short message.
他說，哇，簡訊。
Ross, float on the floor or come over no more.
羅斯，漂浮在地板上，否則就別再過來了。
Sure, your dresser is missing, but this she notices.
當然，你的梳妝臺不見了，但她注意到了。
What?
什麼？
I have to go.
我得走了。
Yeah, Carol should be home by now, so...
是的，卡羅爾現在應該到家了，所以...
How's it going with you guys?
你們怎麼樣？
Well, better, actually.
嗯，實際上更好。
You know, I think I finally figured out
你知道，我想我終於明白了
why we were having so much trouble lately.
為什麼我們最近遇到這麼多麻煩。
Oh, really?
哦真的嗎？
Yeah, you know how I have you guys?
是啊，你們知道我是怎麼擁有你們的嗎？
Well, she doesn't have any close friends that are just hers.
好吧，她沒有任何只屬於她的親密朋友。
But last week she met this woman at the gym, Susan something.
但上週她在健身房遇到了這個女人，蘇珊什麼的。
And they really hit it off,
而且他們真的一拍即合，
and I think it's going to make a difference.
我認為這會有所作為。
So, Eric, what kind of photography do you do?
那麼，艾瑞克，你從事什麼型別的攝影？
Oh, mostly fashion.
哦，主要是時尚。
So there may be models here from time to time.
所以這裡可能時不時就會出現模型。
I hope that's cool.
我希望那很酷。
Yes, it is cool.
是的，這很酷。
Because I have models here, you know.
因為我這裡有模特，你知道。
Never.
絕不。
What else?
還有什麼？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
During the summer,
夏季期間，
I spend most weekends at my sister's beach house,
我大部分週末都在我姐姐的海濱別墅度過
which you are welcome to use, by the way.
順便說一句，歡迎您使用。
Although I should probably tell you she's a porn star.
雖然我應該告訴你她是個色情明星。
Well, listen, I still have one more person to meet,
好吧，聽著，我還有一個人要見，
but unless it turns out to be your sister,
但除非是你的妹妹
I think your chances are pretty good.
我認為你的機會非常好。
All right.
好的。
Bedroom, bathroom, living room,
臥室、衛浴、客廳、
this right here is the kitchen,
這裡是廚房，
and thanks for coming by.
感謝您的光臨。
Bye-bye.
再見。
Don't you, uh, don't you want to ask me any questions?
難道你不想問我任何問題嗎？
Sure.
當然。
Uh, hmm.
呃，嗯。
What's up?
這是怎麼回事？
Well, uh, I'm an actor.
嗯，呃，我是一名演員。
I'm fairly neat.
我還算整潔。
I, uh, I got my own TV.
我，呃，我有自己的電視。
Oh, and don't look at me.
哦，還有別看著我。
Don't worry, I'm totally okay with the gay thing.
別擔心，我完全同意同性戀的事。
What gay thing?
什麼同性戀的事？
Uh, just, you know, in general,
呃，只是，你知道，一般來說，
the whole people being gay thing.
整個人都是同性戀的事。
Totally cool with that.
對此完全很酷。
Well, okay, Jerry, thanks for stopping by.
好吧，傑瑞，謝謝你過來。
Hi.
你好。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey, man.
嘿，夥計。
You want to hear something that sucks?
你想聽一些糟糕的事情嗎？
Do I ever.
我曾經嗎？
Chris says they're closing down the bar.
克里斯說他們要關閉酒吧。
No way.
決不。
Apparently they're turning it into some kind of coffee place.
顯然他們正在把它變成某種咖啡館。
Just coffee?
只是咖啡嗎？
Where are we going to hang out now?
我們現在要去哪裡玩？
Got me.
明白我了。
Can I get a beer, please?
請給我一杯啤酒好嗎？
Hey, did you pick a roommate?
嘿嘿，你選室友了嗎？
You betcha.
你打賭。
Is it the Italian guy?
是那個義大利人嗎？
Yeah, right.
是的，對。
He's so cute.
他真可愛。
Oh, yes, and that's what I want,
哦，是的，這就是我想要的，
a roommate that I can walk around with
一個可以跟我一起走動的室友
and be referred to as the funny one.
並被稱為有趣的人。
The table's free.
桌子是免費的。
Wrap him up.
把他包裹起來。
Be back in just a minute.
一分鐘後就回來。
Get ready for me to whip your butt.
準備好讓我鞭打你的屁股。
Okay, but after that, we're shooting some pool.
好的，但在那之後，我們要拍撞球。
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不，不，不。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Hello.
你好。
Hi.
My friend ordered an onion, not an olive,
我的朋友點了洋蔥，不是橄欖，
and I ordered a rum and Diet Coke,
我點了一杯蘭姆酒和健怡可樂，
which I don't think this is.
我不認為這是。
I am so sorry.
我很抱歉。
That's all right.
沒關係。
I mean, how hard is it to get a couple drinks right, huh?
我的意思是，喝幾杯酒有多難，對吧？
Well, I would like to propose a toast...
好吧，我想提議乾杯…
Go on.
繼續。
...to the woman who, in one year from today,
……致這位女士，從今天起一年後，
will become Mrs. Dr. Barry Barber, DDS.
將成為 Barry Barber 博士夫人，DDS。
I think it's time to see the ring again.
我想是時候再次看到戒指了。
Oh, isn't it exciting?
哦，是不是很興奮呢？
I mean, it's like having a boyfriend for life.
我的意思是，這就像有一個終生的男朋友。
Yeah, I know.
是的，我知道。
Why?
為什麼？
Oh, I don't know.
哦，我不知道。
Well, maybe it's just the idea of Barry for the rest of my life.
好吧，也許這只是巴里我餘生的想法。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I think I...
我想我...
I feel like I need to have one last fling, you know,
我覺得我需要最後一次放縱，你知道，
just to sort of get it out of my system.
只是為了將其從我的系統中刪除。
Rachel, stop.
雷切爾，停下來。
You're so bad.
你太糟糕了。
I'm serious.
我是認真的。
I really...
我真的...
I think I need to just have some meaningless sex, you know,
我想我需要做一些毫無意義的性行為，你知道，
with the next guy I see.
和我見到的下一個人。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
I seem to have dropped my ball.
我好像把球掉了。
Yeah, so?
是啊，所以？
And now I've picked it up again.
現在我又把它撿起來了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I went to high school with her.
我和她一起上高中。
Rachel.
雷切爾。
Hi.
你好。
Monica!
莫妮卡！
Is she giving me the finger?
她在向我豎中指嗎？
Monica!
莫妮卡！
Look.
看。
Hi.
你好。
What do you think?
你怎麼認為？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You can't even see where the Titanic hit it.
你甚至看不到泰坦尼克號撞到的地方。
Yes, his name is Barry.
是的，他的名字叫巴里。
He's a doctor.
他是一名醫生。
Thank you very much.
非常感謝。
Oh, just like you always wanted.
哦，就像你一直想要的那樣。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
Thank you.
謝謝。
So, how about you?
那麼，你呢？
Are you seeing anybody?
你在見人嗎？
Oh, not right now.
哦，現在不行。
Oh, well, that's okay.
哦，好吧，沒關係。
I know.
我知道。
So, I think I'll get back to my friend.
所以，我想我會回到我的朋友身邊。
Oh, yeah, sure, sure, sure.
哦，是的，當然，當然，當然。
Listen, can we please have lunch the next time I'm in the city?
聽著，下次我來城裡的時候我們可以一起吃午餐嗎？
Oh, that'd be great.
哦，那就太好了。
Okay.
好的。
Bye.
再見。
Ten bucks says I never see that woman again in my life.
十塊錢說我這輩子再也見不到那個女人了。
No, honey, really, it's fine.
不，親愛的，真的，沒關係。
Just go with Susan.
就跟蘇珊一起去吧。
Really, I think...
真的，我認為...
No, I think girls' night out is a great idea.
不，我認為女孩之夜是個好主意。
Okay, okay, bye.
好吧好吧，再見。
So, what are they doing?
那麼，他們在做什麼呢？
I don't know, something girly.
我不知道，有點少女感。
Hey, you're early.
嘿嘿，你來早了。
What are you doing with the lamp?
你拿著燈做什麼？
I'm just taking it to get rewired.
我只是拿它來重新接線。
Well, don't take it to the same place you took the stereo,
好吧，不要把它帶到你拿立體聲音響的同一個地方，
because they've had that thing for over a week.
因為他們已經有這樣的事情一個多星期了。
No, no, Mr. Heckles, no one is making any noise up here.
不，不，赫克爾斯先生，這裡沒有人發出任何噪音。
You're disturbing my oboe practice.
你打擾了我的雙簧管練習。
You don't play the oboe.
你不會演奏雙簧管。
I could play the oboe.
我會拉雙簧管。
Then I'm going to have to ask you to keep it down.
那我就得請你小聲一點了。
Who are you?
你是誰？
Hi, I'm Eric, I'm going to be Chandler's new roommate.
嗨，我是艾瑞克，我將成為錢德勒的新室友。
I'm Chandler's new roommate.
我是錢德勒的新室友。
I don't think so.
我不這麼認為。
I could be Chandler's new roommate.
我可以成為錢德勒的新室友。
But he told me over the phone.
但他在電話裡告訴了我。
He told me in person.
他親自告訴我的。
That's weird.
這很奇怪。
Well, I'm going to go into my new apartment now.
好吧，我現在要搬進我的新公寓了。
Then...
然後...
Hi again.
又嗨了。
Hey.
嘿。
Thank you so much.
太感謝了。
Oh, no, no, no, no, don't thank me.
噢，不，不，不，不，別謝我。
Thank the jerk that didn't show up.
感謝那個沒有出現的混蛋。
Okay, I got to get to work.
好吧，我得去上班了。
And not just for the money, but also because every now and then
不只是為了錢，還因為時不時地
somebody walks out of the bathroom with a little bit of toilet paper on their shoe.
有人走出浴室，鞋子上沾著一點衛生紙。
You need some help with that?
你需要一些幫助嗎？
Oh, no, thanks, I got it.
噢，不用了，謝謝，我明白了。
Oh, no, I don't.
哦，不，我不。
Oh, okay.
哦好的。
Stood up too fast, got a little head rush.
站起來太快了，有點頭暈。
The heat.
熱量。
And the humidity.
還有濕度。
That's a tough combination.
這是一個艱難的組合。
Do you want to come in for some lemonade?
你想進來喝點檸檬水嗎？
Like you wouldn't believe.
就像你不會相信一樣。
Wow.
哇。
This is a great place.
這是一個很棒的地方。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Just make yourself comfortable.
只要讓自己舒服就好了。
Gotcha.
明白了。
This place is really nice.
這個地方真的很好。
It's really my grandmother's.
這確實是我祖母的。
I got it from her when she moved to Florida.
當她搬到佛羅裡達時，我從她那裡得到了它。
Otherwise I could never afford a place like this.
否則我永遠買不起這樣的地方。
So if the landlord ever asks,
所以如果樓主問的話
I'm an 87-year-old woman who's afraid of her VCR.
我是一位 87 歲的女士，她害怕她的錄影機。
You thirsty?
你渴嗎？
Oh, you bet I am.
哦，你敢打賭我是。
Okay, here's your penis.
好的，這是你的陰莖。
Oh, my God, what the hell are you doing?
哦，天哪，你到底在做什麼？
You said you want to come in for some lemonade.
你說你想進來喝點檸檬水。
So?
所以？
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Were you just going to give me lemonade?
你只是要給我檸檬水嗎？
Yeah-huh.
是啊哈。
Cover yourself up.
把自己遮起來。
Oh, right, sorry.
哦，對了，抱歉。
I don't believe this.
我不相信這個。
I mean, someone asks you in for lemonade,
我的意思是，有人請你喝檸檬水
and to you that means they want to have sex?
對你來說這意味著他們想要發生性關係？
Um, usually, yeah.
嗯，通常是的。
But not just lemonade.
但不僅僅是檸檬水。
Iced tea, sometimes juice.
冰茶，有時果汁。
Look, I'm sorry.
聽著，我很抱歉。
I just thought you liked me.
我只是以為你喜歡我。
I'm such a jerk.
我真是個混蛋。
It's okay.
沒關係。
I suppose it could happen to anyone.
我想這可能發生在任何人身上。
Not anyone I know, but...
不是我認識的任何人，但是...
By the way, I can still see it.
順便說一句，我仍然可以看到它。
Pheebs.
菲比斯。
Huh?
啊？
Where's your bed?
你的床在哪裡？
It's not in the apartment?
不是在公寓嗎？
Oh, no.
哦，不。
I can't believe this is happening again.
我不敢相信這種事又發生了。
What?
什麼？
Okay, enough of the third degree.
好吧，三級就夠了。
I-I-I don't live here anymore.
我-我-我不再住在這裡了。
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼？
I'm sorry.
對不起。
I-I-I don't live here anymore.
我-我-我不再住在這裡了。
I-I didn't know how to tell you,
我-我不知道該怎麼告訴你，
but, you know, everybody else knows.
但是，你知道，其他人都知道。
Everybody knows?
大家都知道嗎？
That was supposed to be a good thing.
這本來應該是件好事。
I forget why.
我忘了為什麼。
I don't understand this.
我不明白這一點。
I thought we were doing so much better lately.
我認為我們最近做得好多了。
Yeah, because I moved out.
是的，因為我搬出去了。
Monica, I...
莫妮卡，我...
Do you know, okay, do you know,
你知道嗎，好吧，你知道嗎，
I couldn't sleep for, like, a month
我大概一個月無法入睡
because I got, like, a dot of ink
因為我有一點墨水
on one of the sofa cushions?
在其中一個沙發墊上？
Well, you could have just turned the cushion over.
好吧，你可以把墊子翻過來。
I would have, except I had a big spaghetti stain
我會的，除非我有一大塊義大利麵汙漬
on the other side.
在另一邊。
What?
什麼？
Okay, this is what I'm talking about.
好吧，這就是我要說的。
This. I-I need to live in a land
這。我-我需要生活在一片土地上
where people can spill.
人們可能會洩漏的地方。
You can spill?
可以灑嗎？
In the sink?
在水槽裡？
Oh, honey, it's not your fault.
哦，親愛的，這不是你的錯。
You know, this is who you are.
你知道，這就是你。
And I love you.
我愛你。
And I want us to be friends,
我希望我們成為朋友
and if I keep living here,
如果我繼續住在這裡
I don't see that happening.
我不認為這種情況會發生。
I love you, too.
我也愛你。
Oh, good.
哦，很好。
What?
什麼？
What? I'm just sad.
什麼？我只是很難過。
No, you're not.
不，你不是。
You're wondering which cushion it is.
您想知道它是什麼墊子。
Well, why can't I think of both?
好吧，為什麼我不能兩個都想到呢？
I mean, I can think two things.
我的意思是，我可以想到兩件事。
Go ahead. Look. You know you want to.
前進。看。你知道你想要。
Go.
去。
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
So, uh, what you watching?
那麼，呃，你在看什麼？
Baywatch.
海灘救護隊。
What's it about?
是關於什麼的？
Lifeguards.
救生員。
Well, that sounds kind of stoop.
嗯，聽起來有點彎腰。
Who's she?
她是誰？
Nicole Eggert.
妮可·艾格特。
You like her.
你喜歡她。
Wow, look at them run.
哇，看他們跑起來。
They do that a lot.
他們經常這樣做。
Hey, you want a beer?
嘿，你想喝啤酒嗎？
Yeah, I'll go get one.
是的，我去買一個。
No, no, don't get up.
不，不，別起來。
I got a cooler right here.
我這裡有一個冷卻器。
Okay.
好的。
Hello.
你好。
Hey.
嘿。
Do you have any beers? We're out of beers.
你們有啤酒嗎？我們的啤酒沒了。
Help yourself.
幫助自己。
You okay?
你還好嗎？
Phoebe moved out.
菲比搬出去了。
Right.
正確的。
I don't understand.
我不明白。
Am I so hard to live with?
我有那麼難相處嗎？
Is this why I don't have a boyfriend?
這就是我沒有男友的原因嗎？
No.
不。
You don't have a boyfriend because...
你沒有男朋友是因為...
I don't know why you don't have a boyfriend.
我不知道你為什麼沒有男朋友。
You should have a boyfriend.
你應該有個男朋友。
I think so.
我想是的。
Oh, come here.
哦，過來吧。
Come here.
過來吧。
Listen.
聽。
You are one of my favorite people
你是我最喜歡的人之一
and the most beautiful woman I've ever known in real life.
也是我在現實生活中認識的最美麗的女人。
All right.
好的。
Where is everybody?
大家都在哪裡？
Oh, it's already closed.
哦，已經關門了。
Chris gave me the keys to lock up.
克里斯給了我鎖門的鑰匙。
What is wrong?
怎麼了？
My marriage.
我的婚姻。
I think my marriage is, um...
我想我的婚姻是，嗯...
It's kind of over.
有點結束了。
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Why?
為什麼？
Because Carol's a lesbian.
因為卡羅爾是女同性戀。
And...
還有...
And I'm not one.
而我不是其中之一。
And apparently it's not a mix-and-match situation.
顯然這不是一個混合搭配的情況。
Oh, God.
哦，上帝。
I don't believe it.
我不相信。
Oh, you poor bunny.
哦，你這可憐的兔子。
I'm an idiot.
我是個白痴。
I mean, I should have seen it.
我的意思是，我應該看到它。
I mean, Carol and I would be out and she'd...
我是說，卡蘿和我會出去，而她會...
She'd see some beautiful woman and...
她會看到一些美麗的女人，然後…
And she'd be,
而她會是，
Ross, you know, look at her.
羅斯，你知道，看看她。
And I'd think,
我想，
God, my wife is cool.
天哪，我的妻子很酷。
Hey, do you think that Susan person is her lover?
嘿，你認為蘇珊那個人是她的情人嗎？
Well, now I do.
好吧，現在我知道了。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Seven years.
七年了。
I mean, we've been together seven years.
我的意思是，我們已經在一起七年了。
She's the only woman who's ever loved me.
她是唯一一個愛過我的女人。
She's the only woman I've ever...
她是我這輩子唯一的女人
Oh, Ross.
哦，羅斯。
Mmm, this is nice.
嗯，這很好。
I know it is, isn't it?
我知道是這樣，不是嗎？
No, I mean it. This feels really good.
不，我是認真的。這感覺真好。
Is it 100% cotton?
是100%棉嗎？
Yeah, and I got it on sale, too.
是的，我也有賣。
I mean, it looks nubby, but...
我的意思是，它看起來很笨拙，但是...
But it's not.
但事實並非如此。
Anyway, I should go.
無論如何，我該走了。
One of the lifeguards was just about to dismantle a nuclear device.
一名救生員正準備拆除核子裝置。
Well, if you want to get a drink later, we can.
好吧，如果你想稍後喝一杯，我們可以。
Oh, yeah, that sounds great.
哦，是的，聽起來很棒。
Okay.
好的。
Oh, and listen, it's gonna be...
哦，聽著，這將會是...
I know.
我知道。
Thanks.
謝謝。
Maybe this wouldn't have happened if I'd been more nurturing,
如果我更細心的話，也許這一切就不會發生
or I'd paid more attention,
或者我更關注，
or I'd had a uterus.
或者我有一個子宮。
I can't believe it.
我簡直不敢相信。
No, no, you don't deserve this. You don't, Ross.
不，不，你不值得這樣。你不知道，羅斯。
You're really... You're so good.
你真的……你真好。
Thanks.
謝謝。
And you're so sweet. Thanks.
你真是太可愛了。謝謝。
And you're kind.
而且你很友善。
Thanks.
謝謝。
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等，等等，等等，等等。
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等，等等，等等。
My foot is stuck in the pocket.
我的腳卡在口袋裡了。
What?
什麼？
I can't get it out.
我拿不出來。
That's not something a girl wants to hear.
這可不是一個女孩願意聽到的。
No.
不。
Don't start.
不要開始。
Ow.
噢。
What?
什麼？
Stupid balls are in the way.
愚蠢的球擋住了路。
Hmm.
唔。
Oh, well.
那好吧。
That probably wouldn't have been the most constructive solution.
這可能不是最具建設性的解決方案。
You have chalk on your face.
你臉上有粉筆。
Hmm?
唔？
Uh, Ross, you're right. I don't know why.
呃，羅斯，你說得對。我不知道為什麼。
I always thought this was real grass.
我一直以為這是真草。
Uh...
呃...
Honey, you okay?
親愛的，你還好嗎？
My wife's a lesbian.
我妻子是女同性戀。
Cool.
涼爽的。
Ross, Joey, Joey, Ross.
羅斯，喬伊，喬伊，羅斯。
Hey, what's going on?
嘿，發生什麼事了？
I can't believe you came back.
我不敢相信你回來了。
Don't say anything.
什麼也別說。
I don't want to speak.
我不想說話。
I don't want to think.
我不想去想。
I just want you to take me and kiss me
我只想讓你帶我親吻我
and make love to me right here, right now.
就在此時此地與我做愛。
Rachel.
雷切爾。
Rachel!
雷切爾！
What?
什麼？
You missed the exit.
你錯過了出口。
Oh.
哦。
Sorry.
對不起。
My God, what were you thinking about?
天哪，你在想什麼？
Hmm.
唔。
Um...
嗯...
Barry?
巴里？
Aw.
噢。